{
    "subject": "resource/Here_Comes_the_Navy",
    "predicate": "property/writer",
    "object": "resource/Earl_Baldwin",
    "human_readable": "The writer of Here Comes the Navy is Earl Baldwin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8399051427841187,
            "question": "Is Earl Baldwin a songwriter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7048422694206238,
            "question": "What is the name of the author of 'Here Comes the Navy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6872562170028687,
            "question": "Who wrote the song 'Here Comes the Navy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6089781522750854,
            "question": "When was 'Here Comes the Navy' probably written?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4358716905117035,
            "question": "What is Earl Baldwin known for besides songwriting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4166586101055145,
            "question": "Can you name any other songs written by Earl Baldwin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39326682686805725,
            "question": "Is there a story behind the song 'Here Comes the Navy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3488663136959076,
            "question": "Could you find any lyrics from 'Here Comes the Navy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2874482572078705,
            "question": "Are there any famous recordings of 'Here Comes the Navy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19440816342830658,
            "question": "What genre is the song 'Here Comes the Navy' likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The writer of Here Comes the Navy is Earl Baldwin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6689_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous recordings of 'Here Comes the Navy'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6689_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you find any lyrics from 'Here Comes the Navy'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6689_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a story behind the song 'Here Comes the Navy'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6689_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6689_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6689_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6689_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6689_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6689_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6689_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6689_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6689_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6689_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6689_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information states that \"Here Comes the Navy\" was written by Earl Baldwin and Ben Markson. Therefore, the statement that Earl Baldwin is one of the writers of \"Here Comes the Navy\" is correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}